<resources>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!--AppStuff-->
    <string name="app_name">LiquiCalc</string>
    <string name="by_author">by Toni Zinke</string>

    <!--CalcActivity-->
    <!--TextViews-->
    <string name="zielkonzentration"><u>Zielkonzentration</u></string>
    <string name="zielmenge"><u>Zielmenge</u></string>
    <string name="shotkonzentration"><u>Shotkonzentration</u></string>
    <string name="aromakonzentration"><u>Aromakonzentration</u></string>

    <string name="percentSign">%</string>
    <string name="nikotinUnit">mg/ml</string>
    <string name="milliliterUnit">ml</string>

    <!--Buttons-->
    <string name="calcButtonText">Berechnen</string>

    <!--CalcResult-->
    <string name="aromamenge">Aromamenge</string>
    <string name="shotmenge">Shotmenge</string>

    <!--ToolTips-->
    <string name="tooltipMenge">Wie viel Liquid wird gemischt?</string>
    <string name="tooltipKonz">Wie viel Nikotin soll enthalten sein?</string>
    <string name="tooltipShotKonz">Wie viel Nikotin ist in dem Shot enthalten?(steht auf der Packung)</string>
    <string name="tooltipAroma">Wie viel Aroma soll in das  Liquid?(steht auf der Aromaflasche)</string>

    <!--ResultSummary-->

    <!--Navigation-->
    <string name="nav_item_calc">Rechner</string>
    <string name="nav_item_notices">Hinweise</string>
    <string name="nav_item_aboutme">Über mich</string>
    <string name="nav_group_communication">Kommunikation</string>
    <string name="nav_item_share">Teilen</string>

    <!--ContentDescription-->
    <string name="deco">decoration</string>

    <!--HinweisActivity-->
    <string name="action_clear">Felder leeren</string>
    <string name="large_text">Lorizzle ipsum dolizzle sit amizzle, consectetizzle adipiscing check it out. Fo shizzle mah nizzle fo rizzle, mah home g-dizzle fo velit, funky fresh volutpat, pimpin quis, gravida vizzle, pot. Dope eget cool. Sizzle erizzle. Fusce izzle dang dapibizzle check it out tempus fizzle. Maurizzle pellentesque nibh dizzle hizzle. Vestibulum in tortizzle. Pellentesque dang rhoncus dizzle. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Donec dapibizzle. Curabitizzle tellus mammasay mammasa mamma oo sa, owned crackalackin, mattizzle ac, eleifend break yo neck, yall, . Owned suscipit. Fo sheezy velit pot dang.
Phasellizzle interdum volutpat tellizzle. Ut check it out adipiscing owned. Donec non est. Nulla funky fresh own yo, uhuh ... yih! nec, accumsizzle dawg, fermentizzle quizzle, dang. Check it out nizzle funky fresh. Etizzle rutrum ornare ante. Mauris pizzle. Boofron izzle pede varius nibh black commodo. Rizzle fo shizzle mah nizzle fo rizzle, mah home g-dizzle dolor fo shizzle mah nizzle fo rizzle, mah home g-dizzle my shizz, consectetuer adipiscing elizzle. Shiznit izzle stuff. Quisque its fo rizzle , sodalizzle et, i saw beyonces tizzles and my pizzle went crizzle a, get down get down a, im in the shizzle.
Curabitizzle shut the shizzle up stuff quis nisi yo mollizzle. My shizz potenti. Daahng dawg shut the shizzle up. Dizzle neque. Crackalackin orci. Thats the shizzle black mauris, interdizzle rizzle, feugizzle sit mah nizzle, malesuada izzle, thats the shizzle. Pellentesque ma nizzle. Vestibulum orci mi, check it out in, sagittis sizzle, break it down sempizzle, shit. Crizzle izzle ipsum. Mammasay mammasa mamma oo sa volutpat yo mamma vizzle orci. Get down get down shizzle my nizzle crocodizzle justo uhuh ... yih! purus sodalizzle ornare. Sed venenatizzle crazy the bizzle lacus. Mofo urna. Hizzle venenatizzle placerat dope. Curabitur eu ante. Mofo pharetra, shiznit crackalackin fo shizzle hendrerizzle, ipsum felizzle elementizzle sem, izzle aliquizzle gangster thats the shizzle luctizzle doggy. Nam a . Shiz aptent taciti sociosqu izzle bizzle torquent per conubia sizzle, pizzle inceptizzle hymenizzle. Fo shizzle interdum, neque hizzle da bomb owned, boom shackalack dizzle viverra leo, in own yo risus dawg im in the shizzle sem.
Phat nizzle mauris black pot consectetuer pretizzle. Vivamus mofo i saw beyonces tizzles and my pizzle went crizzle shizzle my nizzle crocodizzle. Nam bling bling nisl eget dang auctor feugizzle. Shiz suscipizzle shiz ghetto. Break yo neck, yall izzle arcu. Ghetto boofron enizzle, dizzle sizzle, mah nizzle eu, yippiyo bow wow wow, libero. Nullizzle shiz dizzle nizzle shizzle my nizzle crocodizzle posuere pharetra. Quisque pede i saw beyonces tizzles and my pizzle went crizzle, da bomb pulvinar, auctizzle brizzle, mollizzle sizzle amizzle, erizzle. Sheezy boom shackalack daahng dawg. Mah nizzle pizzle purus, elementizzle mah nizzle, sollicitudizzle in, consequizzle ma nizzle, turpizzle. Im in the shizzle a shizzle my nizzle crocodizzle eu rizzle rutrum the bizzle. Curabitur accumsan sagittis crazy. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus izzle netizzle da bomb malesuada famizzle sheezy pot egestizzle. In est. Ma nizzle im in the shizzle. Ut erizzle gangster, semper quis, suscipit ac, porta owned, nisl. Pimpin sagittizzle gravida velizzle.
Maecenas at stuff. Nizzle fo shizzle mah nizzle fo rizzle, mah home g-dizzle. Proin fo shizzle, break yo neck, yall non congue consectetuer, metus fizzle consequat purizzle, you son of a bizzle ullamcorper dui ma nizzle non funky fresh. Shizzlin dizzle faucibus elit. Break it down nibh lectizzle, consequat sed, ornare volutpat, porttitor dope, tellus. Proin sed boom shackalack. Stuff condimentum mi in nibh. Bow wow wow hendrerizzle thats the shizzle felis. Fo shizzle mah nizzle fo rizzle, mah home g-dizzle crunk fo a erat. Etiam bow wow wow away mofo. Ut mauris. Bizzle nisl metizzle, euismod sizzle, stuff sed, gangsta vizzle, nisi. Vivamizzle boom shackalack consectetizzle nisl.
    Nunc sure black izzle urna. Shizznit fizzle. Things pot boofron dui. Owned sit fizzle purus eu break it down condimentizzle. Suspendisse potenti. Nunc at fizzle vitae tellivizzle tincidunt aliquam. Break yo neck, yall gravida tempizzle shut the shizzle up. In interdum erat et sizzle. Crackalackin malesuada. Nizzle vitae tellus sizzle we gonna chung sizzle get down get down. Nulla facilisi. Nullizzle bow wow wow quizzle a massa sizzle pulvinar. I saw beyonces tizzles and my pizzle went crizzle ma nizzle fizzle shizzlin dizzle velizzle. Cras the bizzle metizzle sed tellizzle. Etiam pretizzle doggy nizzle dui. Gangster rutrizzle rhoncizzle purus.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notice">Hinweise</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
